<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Findings on UVA Biocomplexity Institute</title>
    <link>/findings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Findings on UVA Biocomplexity Institute</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/findings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Economics</title>
      <link>/findings/economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/economics/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */h1, h2, h3 {text-align: center;}Economic ProfileThe current maps represent an overview of the city of Petersburg, VA and as you see they have large economic disparities. As I direct your attention closer to the map on the right you will see there is High Amounts of residents living below the poverty line and only one area that has houses only 10% below the poverty line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health</title>
      <link>/findings/health/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/health/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */h1, h2, h3 {text-align: center;}Health OutcomesThe city of Petersburg is currently ranked last for health outcomes in the state of Virginia. Obesity is at a all time high with 40% and Diabetes is at a high of 14.6% which you see the graphs on the right show just how high they are in comparison to the entire state and national percentages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transportation</title>
      <link>/findings/transportation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/transportation/</guid>
      <description>Main FindingLocal commuting score#### Driving#### Public Transit#### Biking#### Walking[walkability score]
Conclusion and Policy ImplicationsKeeping in mind that most of the city of petersburg lives below the poverty line we decided to take a look at the community options available. Most people preferred a car as there preferred means of transportation and in a household most owned at least one car. The average person in a household in the city is 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crime and Policy</title>
      <link>/findings/crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/crime/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */h1, h2, h3 {text-align: center;}CrimeKeeping safety in mind we decided to take a look at the current state of the city’s crime. We found that the city of Petersburg,Va is currently ranked the most dangerous city in Virginia. The chart on the right hand side shows a breakdown of the type of crimes and their comparison to Virginia overall and the national stats.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>