<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UVA Biocomplexity Institute</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on UVA Biocomplexity Institute</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Background</title>
      <link>/data-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/data-methods/</guid>
      <description>While this page is optional, it probably makes sense to have one weighted at the top (see the front matter at the top of this Rmd file) that gives a general overview of the project. This could be something like the final poster while the other pages highlight more in-depth observations. Here is a general schema of what should be covered throughout your website:
Variables[Race][Age][Poverty][income][Education Levels][crime data][jobs/industries/economics]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economics</title>
      <link>/findings/economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/economics/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */h1, h2, h3 {text-align: center;}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health and Wellbeing</title>
      <link>/findings/health/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/health/</guid>
      <description>Main Findings[Here you will describe the results and include important visualizations from your project.]
Conclusion and Policy Implications[Here you could highlight the main takeaways and the potential policy implications of your findings.]
References[List your references here using APA format (or at least standardize all of the references using the same format).]
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transportation</title>
      <link>/findings/transportation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/transportation/</guid>
      <description>Main Findinglocal commuting score#### Driving#### Public Transit#### Biking#### Walking[walkability score]
Conclusion and Policy Implications[Here you could highlight the main takeaways and the potential policy implications of your findings.]
References[List your references here using APA format (or at least standardize all of the references using the same format).]
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/</guid>
      <description>UVA Data Science for the Public Good Program The Data Science for the Public Good (DSPG) Young Scholars program is a summer immersive program held at the Biocomplexity Institute’s Social and Decision Analytics division (SDAD). In its seventh year, the program engages students from across the country to work together on projects that address state, federal, and local government challenges around critical social issues relevant in the world today. DSPG young scholars conduct research at the intersection of statistics, computation, and the social sciences to determine how information generated within every community can be leveraged to improve quality of life and inform public policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/overview/</guid>
      <description>FOLARFriends of Lower Appomattox River, or FOLAR, is a nonprofit organization actively working to preserve, protect, and enhance the Lower Appomattox River for all to enjoy.
Collective Impact: Developing a regional common agenda around creating and protecting the Appomattox River and Trail to positively impact public health, safety, and community prosperity.
Appomattox River TrailThe Appomattox River Trail is a 25 mile long trail along the lower Appomattox River with access points connecting to boat access, parks, and other riverside trails.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>